Because of a disappointed cold
I once knew
That's what my mom said back then, Yudo-ah.
uh
you
I remembered
What are you talking about?
You remembered
That
It was an accident
I got drunk a lot
You just have no choice
inevitably
Let's pretend it never happened
I don't want to be awkward
leave
ha
Got it
Let's pretend it never happened
I don't want to be awkward
With you
Okay
Ah
Ah, the elevator
ha
uh
Ugh
Oh, what gi are you already wearing?
Hey man
Then it is the beginning of three eras.
Then you should wear it symbolically.
How about
Honestly, it's kind of cool.
You're laughing
I'll take a picture for you as a souvenir.
Stand over there
Hey, thank you for the flowerpot.
Now
one two three
Fighting for the first time
different poses
Listen to the trophy too
I have to smile
Now one two three
It was an accident
I got drunk a lot
You just have no choice
inevitably
Let's pretend it never happened
I don't want to be awkward
With you
Next time, I'll buy real food.
Why don't you come to the gym?
I like that person
who
Team leader
Yeah
I
I don't like you eating with just anyone
Are you okay for lunch tomorrow?
I will really buy you food
yes
good
Oh, I'm here
mom
What's going on without even saying a word?
I came here because I was afraid you might starve to death.
Oh my, what does this refrigerator look like?
I always drink water and beer
You like braised ribs
It's okay
If it's hard, say it's hard
Because mom is here
I'm totally fine
I've had a lot of interviews and been asked to come.
Oh my, I got cut.
I thought you'd cry and cry, but you're all grown up now
My son haha
My mom is good at braised ribs.
You can do anything only if you eat well
Eat well and don’t worry
sit
eat a lot
I will eat well
Oh, but is the dog at home?
Dog also likes braised ribs.
I have to ask him to come and eat with me.
Oh no, he's not home right now.
uh
I think it's there
No, no, don't do it.
Baby, why are you two fighting?
no
Me and my mom
Because I want to eat in privacy
Then eat everything first and then bring it to me.
I tried a lot to give opinions.
Uh oh
don't press
Let's just leave it alone
What is it
Standing in front of the door without even ringing the doorbell
Did you want to leave me without even telling me?
I thought you weren't home
Why aren't you exercising?
Don't even answer
Ah
I'm just a little tired
I'm going
Burn it and eat it
Ah
Yudoah
I can't even lie
Is towing okay?
brother
what are you doing
I need to train more ah
Because the master is too good at it.
What's going on
I'm so combative these days
hello
Oh Karam
You came a little early today.
I have to exercise hard
To win
Ah
Oh that's right
Well, better than it looks
Your competitive spirit is no joke.
yes
I have everything I want
I lost my senses
I'm going to take a shower. Yes.
Then today
Let’s try eye hair
Teacher Haneul, I think you're having a hard time right now.
Could you teach me?
Oh, I'm fine.
I'll do it for you
Hey, you need to rest too.
I think you're still breathing hard.
If you get caught wrong,
My bones are falling out
It's okay
I'm not going out
I'm going out
Members, we
The class where the teacher only does sparring.
I'll let you know
I have no courage. Let’s just be friends like now.
That's the way to keep seeing
You should know
what are you
me
People who like Yudo Ah
Don't touch it
Well, next time it's really going to go out.
I don't know
Who will get hurt?
I guess I'm not confident
Just cowardly circling around
Let's stop
I have no courage. Let’s just be friends like now.
me
People who like Yudo Ah
It's home
No, I'm Park
Mr. Doha
Team leader
The weather is nice today
You look in a good mood today.
Doha ate today
It's a day to live
Ah
Come to a place like this too
yes
This is my favorite restaurant.
The team leader only goes to a restaurant or something.
I thought you were going
I'm not alone today
The two of you came
your grandmother
who buys food
They said they would give it to me, so I came with it.
What I eat every day
Oh, and give me some kimchi pancakes too.
Team leader, I am clam kalguksu
I'm older than you.
my name
Not the team leader
This is my first time bringing someone with me.
Oh my
I don't even know the older person's name.
Did you come together?
Oh my, I’m so sad.
Oh, I know, older team leader.
You are no longer the team leader
Call me older
It's okay to call him my brother
Ah
Yes team leader
Oh no
I'll wait until it gets easier.
yes
You look so different today
Where are you going
Just
Smile a lot, unlike at work
Is that so?
There is someone who can see well
There's someone you like
yes
for a long time
I just watched
um
Do you have plans for dinner?
yes
You could say so.
thank you
There's more delicious food
Eat quickly before you wash.
What are you worried about?
yes
no
continue today
What do you think you're thinking?
Ah
It's not like that
If you have any concerns, tell me everything
I'll pretend not to hear you
1 degree
Something else too
whatever
It's okay
tell me
The team leader
Ah
no
Mr. Phenomenon
My brother
Because I'm good at everything
Who do you like?
I'm in a relationship
You'll be good at all of those things, too.
I'm a moose
I don't know what will happen
It's difficult for me too
I like it because I want to look good
Take me to the restaurant
But that restaurant
This is a restaurant my grandmother knows.
What if I hate it?
Should I just go to a restaurant?
I'm thinking about it
Ah, I see you in the evening.
The person who wanted to look good earlier
yes
that person
This is Doha.
But now I
Do something you haven't done before
I'm going to try it
Doha Lee
I like it a lot
Mr. older man
Mr. Doha
why did you like it
Coffee came out
thank you
Team leader
hand
Are you okay?
It's okay
I was going to buy you coffee
I got a wound on my chin.
I spilled it all
Haha
Because your smile is pretty